bartermyfunds.com 2019-05-17

# Barter My Funds

Your privacy is important to Bartermyfunds. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Bartermyfunds collects, and the ways in which Bartermyfunds uses that personal information.

### Personal information collection

Bartermyfunds may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide us with for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * information that you provide us with for the purpose of subscribing to the website's services;
  * any other information that you send to Bartermyfunds.

### Using personal information

Bartermyfunds may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website's services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send you marketing communications.

In the case where Bartermyfunds discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Bartermyfunds may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

### Securing your data

Bartermyfunds will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Bartermyfunds will store all the personal information you provide.

### Cross-border data transfers

Information that Bartermyfunds collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Bartermyfunds operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

### Updating this statement

Bartermyfunds reserves the right to update or modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

### Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

Bartermyfunds is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

### Contact Bartermyfunds

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Bartermyfunds' treatment of your personal information, please write by email to info@Bartermyfunds.com
